who had a deep desire to feel haunted
today biohybrid robot hand made from
human muscle tissue yes we are making
humans in peace meal and turning them
into biohybrid robotics you guys
remember the flesh thing the human skin
that could smile and could become a
living healing skin for robots and of
course the robots that were made
literally with human brains operating
them well now we can make limbs that are
able to move like a human's hand because
they're made out of human muscle tissue
that operates that hand this is
something that roboticists and
biologists have been working on together
for quite some time Robotics are flawed
we're trying to take something and make
it look like biological systems when
biology had billions of years to evolve
it replicating the tactile sensation in
movement that we have in our own hands
is very difficult so why not just borrow
from biology or state plagiarized in
this case one of the problems with
growing muscle tissue is that it tends
to suffer from hypoxia and become
necrotic our muscles are very hungry
things so what they did with these guys
they grew them in cell culture one
strand at a time and that cell culture
gives them oxygen and nutrients as they
grow once they put together multiple
sheets they could then take it and fold
it in on itself to make muscle fibers
similar to our own the result is
something that can be controlled with
electrical impulses not not too
dissimilar to how our own muscle tissues
work they do suffer from the same
problems that trying to grow human
brains to operate robots also suffer
from and that's going to be
vascularizing them although the
technology is rapidly getting better
right now they're still going to have to
provide them with a medium that they can
get oxygen and nutrients from directly
from diffusion so it absorbs it directly
from the outside environment ultimately
the combination of these things could be
used for amputees something with a
living skin that feels and grows and
heals but it could also make robots that
are more human without actually needing
a human I think what we're really doing
is Bridging the Gap between humans and
machines we know that brain organoid
technology could be used with brain
implant technology the same things that
allows us to operate them like computers
could allow us to operate our own brains
like computers robots can't do a lot of
the things that we do robots have a
difficult time with crochet for example
interestingly enough crocheting
artificial muscle fibers can make
something that functions very much like
our muscle fibers I always thought that
when we're trying to make technology we
should borrow from nature turns out
plagiarizing nature does work too brain
organoids can do a lot of things that AI
can't they have a different kind of
creativity they especially learn spatial
recognition better than our current AI
models a lot of the push for these guys
comes from them being less power hungry
than
ai ai needs a whole nuclear power plant
technically they might need a pack of
sugar it's not that simple but the
combination with AI May create something
that we never could have imagined I do
describe this as making humans in peace
meal you can't clone a person in much of
the world but you can clone their
individual components and combine them
with robotics people always like to ask
if researchers read sci-fi yes they do a
lot of inspiration comes from science
fiction the question isn't why so much a
lot of uses come after the fact brain
organoids were made before we found a
lot of uses for them this technology too
will find uses for after the fact it
will be interesting to see how we can
overcome the limitations of human
biology in robots like infection and
aging the push to have more efficient
robots may end up with medicine that
makes our meat robots our FLH Mecca more
efficient it is creepy that is hard to
deny but science is modern day magic
that's what it does it pushes the limits
of what is possible we're just going to
have to see how history looks at it